Studious Beyonders,
Today's mysticism lesson is packed with knowledge.
Pay attention to what you see and hear,
jot down any questions you have,
and wait until everything is over before consulting me.
Ah
Do you still remember Dunn inviting Klein to become a Beyonder
and letting him choose a Pathway?
This is exactly the first piece of mysticism knowledge for today's lesson.
Beyonder Pathways,
Beyonder Pathways are a Beyonder's power system.
They comprise a total of 22 Pathways,
which can be understood as 22 types of professsions.
Every Pathway is comprised of different Sequences,
which can be understood as different ranks.
The smaller the Sequence number,
the stronger the corresponding abilities.
Beyonders can drink the corresponding potion
to raise their Sequence level.
And each time their Sequence level advances,
they not only gain new Beyonder abilities
but their existing abilities are also be enhanced.
Additionally, each Sequence
has corresponding acting principles and promotion rituals,
which constrain and guide the growth of those on a Pathway.
Now here's a question,
if you were to become a Beyonder
which Pathway would you chose?
Hahaha,
Next, let me introduce the Nighthawks,
which is also the organization I belong to.
The Nighthawks
are affiliated with the Church of the Evernight Goddess.
As an official Beyonder organziation,
they are responsible for handling supernatural incidents within the Loen Kingdom.
对抗邪教与隐秘组织
以及自身对抗魔药带来的失控风险
我所在的廷根值夜者小队
主要负责的是廷根市北区
西区和金梧桐区等区域
与女神信徒相关的超自然事件
目前正式队员有队长邓恩
伦纳德、弗莱、洛耀
科恩黎和西迦
文职人员有我、罗珊、布莱特
以及刚刚加入值夜者小队
暂时挂靠文职人员的克莱恩
哈哈哈对了
对外介绍
记得说我们是黑荆棘安保公司啊
偶尔我们也会接一些找猫
找狗的委托小任务
赚到钱可是有不少额外补贴的哦
下面我开始教你神秘领域最常见
掌握最简单
后续也最有前途的能力
灵视
灵视是非凡者通过灵性感知灵界
观察目标气场与灵体的能力
用灵视
除了能直接看到一些灵体，鬼魂和怨灵
还能看到别人的以太体
通过它不同的厚度、亮度、颜色
来判断对方的健康和情绪状态
如果灵视提升
或者神秘学知识掌握的更多
还能以此判断对方的寿命长短
内层的星灵体
对应颜色表示当前的情绪
红色热情亢奋
蓝色冷静处在思考之中
白色光明积极向上
暗色忧郁悲伤沉默
紫色则表示灵性占据主导
冷淡疏离
聪明的年轻人们
今天的神秘学课堂就到这里啦
最后我要留给你们一个作业
开启你们的灵视
看看我当前的情绪是怎样的